Guide to the Wells Rich Greene Inc. Records, 1954-1998 and undated RL.01365
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1954-1998 and undated (Acc. 98-0396), 140 boxes
  - Video and Film
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 24)
      - 82. Corporate--Washington Week in Review Escort Billboard. 1986. TRT: :20 (Box 24)
      - 83. Ford Motor Co.--Driver Rev. 3. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 24)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 25)
      - 84. Corporate--3 spots. 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 25)
      - 85. Ford Motor Co.--Workers & Warranties. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 86. Ford Motor Co.--3 spots. 1986. TRT: 1:30 (Box 25)
      - 87. Corporate--2 spots--Washington Week In Review Opening Billboard--Thunderbird & Mustang. 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 25)
      - 88. Corporate--Washington Week In Review Opening Billboard--Thunderbird. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 89. Insta-Clear (glass) --Cold Room. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 90. Corporate--Winter. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 91. Corporate--Employees/ Durability. 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 25)
      - 92. Ford 2 spots. 1987. TRT: 1:30 (Box 25)
      - 93. Corporate--Employees/ Warranty. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 94. Ford Corp.--3 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:00 (Box 25)
      - 95. Corporate--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:30 (Box 25)
      - 96. Corporate--2 spots. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
      - 97. Corporate--4 spots. 1987. TRT: 2:30 (Box 25)
      - 98. Ford Motor Company Corporate--4 spots. 1988. TRT: 2:00 (Box 25)
      - 99. Ford Motor Company Corporate--Dependability Rev. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 25)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 26)
      - 100. Corporate--Dealer Service Rev. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 26)
      - 101. Corporate--Crawl 88. 1988. TRT: :15 (Box 26)
      - 102. Corporate--Dependability 88. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 26)
      - 103. Corporate--Prevention 88. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 26)
      - 104. Corporate--Prevention 88 Rev. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 26)
      - 105. Corporate--Dependability 88 Rev. 1. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 26)
      - 106. Corporate 4 spots. Circa 1988. TRT: 2:00 (Box 26)
      - 107. Ford Corporate--Quality Cars/ Quality Care. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 26)
      - 108. Corporate--9 Year Quality Crawl. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 26)
      - 113. Corporate--2 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 26)
      - 114. Corporate--2 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 26)
      - 115. Corporate--10th Year Quality Crawl. 1990. TRT: :15 (Box 26)
      - 116. Corp.--4 spots. 1990. TRT: 2:00 (Box 26)
      - 117. Corporate--7 spots. 1991. TRT: 3:30 (Box 26)
      - 117A. Ford Motor Company--7 spots (list enclosed). 1991. TRT: 3:30 (Box 26)
      - 118. Ford Corp.--21 spots. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 26)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 27)
      - 119. Ford Motor Co.--5 spots. 1991. TRT: 3:30 (Box 27)
      - 120. Ford Motor Company--5 spots. 1991. TRT: 3:30 (Box 27)
      - 120A. Ford Motor Co.--4 spots. 1991. TRT: 3:00 (Box 27)
      - 120B. Ford Motor Company--6 spots. 1991. TRT: 3:30 (Box 27)
      - 121. 10 Years. 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 27)
      - 122. Ford--11th Year Quality Crawl. 1991. TRT: :15 (Box 27)
      - 123. Ford--!!th (sic) Year Quality Crawl. 1991. TRT: :15 (Box 27)
      - 124. Ford Corporate--2 spots. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 27)
      - 125. Ford Corp.--2 spots. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 27)
      - 126. Ford--Full-Line / Tarp. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 27)
      - 127. Corporate--Q! Logo (Oval Hand Wipe). 1991. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 27)
      - 128. Ford Corp.--4 spots. 1992. TRT: 2:00 (Box 27)
      - 128A. Ford Motor Company--4 spots. 1992. TRT: 2:00 (Box 27)
      - 129. New Business Jaguar = Ford Montage. 1992. TRT: 4:25 (Box 27)
      - 130. Ford Corp.--2 spots. 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 27)
      - 131. Corporate--Environment 2 versions. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 27)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 28)
      - 132. Corporate--Environment Rev. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 28)
      - 133. Corporate--Paints. 1992. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 28)
      - 134. Corporate-- 2 spots both Bumpers. 1992. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 28)
      - 135. Corporate--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 28)
      - 136. Ford--Quotation Revised Track. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 28)
      - 137. Corporate--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 28)
      - 138. Proposal for Pilot--The American Road. 1993. TRT: 3:17 (Box 28)
      - 139. Corporate--Son of Around the World. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 28)
      - 140. Corporate--Son of Quotation. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 28)
      - 141. Corporate--Son of Quotation. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 28)
      - 142. Ford Corporate--3 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:30 (Box 28)
      - 143. Ford--3 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 28)
      - 144. Ford Corp.--4 spots. 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 28)
      - 145. Ford Motor Company--Corporate--3 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 28)
      - 146. Contour Mercury--2 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 28)
      - 147. Ford Corp.--4 spots. 1994. TRT: 3:00 (Box 28)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 29)
      - 148. Corp. 2 spots. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 29)
      - 148A. Ford--Launch w/ Quality is Job One ending. Circa 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 29)
      - 149. Ford Corp.--4 spots. 1994. TRT: 4:30 (Box 29)
      - 150. Ford Motor Company Corporate.--4 spots. 1995. TRT: 3:00 (Box 29)
      - 151. Ford Corporate--4 spots. 1995. TRT: 2:00 (Box 29)
      - 152. Ford Corporate--3 spots. 1995. TRT: 1:30 (Box 29)
      - 153. Ford Corp.--2 spots. 1995. TRT: 1:00 (Box 29)
      - 154. Ford Motor Co. Corp.--4 spots. 1995. TRT: 3:00 (Box 29)
      - 154A. Ford Motor Co. Corporate.--7 spots. 1995. TRT: 4:00 plus (Box 29)
      - 154B. Ford Motor Co. Corporate.--4 spots ( Master). 1995. TRT: 2:30 (Box 29)
      - 155. Ford Motor Co. Corporate.--4 spots ( Master). 1995. TRT: 2:30 (Box 29)
      - 156. Ford Corp.--2 spots. 1995. TRT: 1:00 (Box 29)
      - 157. Ford Corp.--2 spots. 1995. TRT: 1:00 (Box 29)
      - 158. Ford Corp.--Looks--T (No dogs). 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 29)
      - 158. Ford Corp.--Looks--T. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 29)
      - 159. Ford Corp.--Looks--T / with dog at end. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 29)
    - Ford Motor Company (continued) (Box 30)
      - 160. Ford Corp.--4 spots. 1995. TRT: 3:00 (Box 30)
      - 161. Ford Corp.--2 spots. 1995. TRT: 1:00 (Box 30)
      - 162. Ford Corp.--6 spots. 1995. TRT: 4:30 (Box 30)
      - 163. Ford Corp.--2 spots. 1995. TRT: 1:00 (Box 30)
      - 164. Ford Motor Company Corporate--6 spots. 1996. TRT: 4:30--23:00 (Box 30)
    - Gain (Procter & Gamble)
      - 31. Gain--2 spots. Circa 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 30)
      - 32. Gain--Family Reunion w/Announcer 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 30)
      - 33. Gain--Bobby w/Announcer & Title. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 30)
      - 34. Ultra Gain--3 spots (animatics). 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 30)
      - 35. Ultra Gain Detergent--4 spots (all Scentsation w/variations). 1990. TRT: 2:00 (Box 30)
      - 36. Ultra Gain--Scentsation Retro. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 30)
      - 37. Ultra Gain--2 spots (both Scentsation w/variations). 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 30)
      - 38A. Ultra Gain--Landscaper. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 30)
      - 39. Ultra Gain--Dishwasher ( Master). 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 30)
      - 40. Ultra Gain--The Shirt. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 30)
      - 41. Ultra Gain--Landscape Non-New. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 30)
    - Gain (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (Box 31)
      - 42. Ultra Gain--5 spots. 1991. TRT: 2:30 (Box 31)
      - 43. Ultra Gain--7 spots. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
      - 44. Gain--2 spots (animatics). 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
      - 45. Gain--2 spots (all Tire Seller). 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 31)
      - 46. Gain--That Gain Feeling / New. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 31)
      - 47. Gain--Mover--w/ Powder Shot. 1991. TRT: :28.5 (Box 31)
      - 48. Ultra Gain--4 spots. 1991. TRT: Circa 4:00 (Box 31)
      - 49. Ultra Gain--3 spots. 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 31)
      - 50. Ultra Gain--Proof Sweatshirt / Powder. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 31)
      - 51 & 55. Gain. Circa 1992. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 31)
      - 52. Liquid Ultra Gain--2 spots (both Liquid Sunshine). 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
      - 53. Gain--Dirty Shirt. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 31)
      - 54. Ultra Gain--2 spots (both Proof/ Sweatshirt). 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
      - 56. Gain with Bleach--Ironing II. 1992. TRT: :40 (Box 31)
      - 57. Ultra Gain--2 spots (both Scentsation Retro Rev. 2). 1992. TRT: 1:00 (Box 31)
      - 58. Gain--3 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:47 (Box 31)
    - Gain (Procter & Gamble) (continued) (see box 85 for 5 more Gains) (Box 32)
      - 59. Gain with Bleach--2 spots (both Ironing Morph). 1993. TRT: :45 (Box 32)
      - 60. Gain--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:15 (Box 32)
      - 61. Ultra Liquid Gain--What Gets In II Rev. 3. 1993. TRT: :35 (Box 32)
      - 62. Liquid Gain--That Gain Family / Full Test. 1993. TRT: :33 (Box 32)
      - 63. Gain--2 spots (both Take It Off). 1993. TRT: 1:02 (Box 32)
      - 64. Gain Laundry Detergent--Loretta / Inside Out. 1993. TRT: :31 (Box 32)
      - 65. Gain--2 spots (both Morph). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 32)
      - 66. Gain--2 spots (both Morph). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 32)
      - 67. Gain Detergent--Super Yard Worker. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 32)
      - 68. Gain with Bleach--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 32)
      - 69. Gain--2 spots (test only). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 32)
    - General Mills
      - Historical Reel (list enclosed--38 spots). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 32)
    - Heineken
      - Black Adder--9 spots (list included). 1996. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 32)
      - Client Vers. Edited Dub Master--13 spots (list included). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 32)
      - Heineken--6 spots (list included. 1997. TRT: 3:00 (Box 32)
      - Heineken-- Master--25 spots (list included). 1995-1997. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 32)
      - Heineken Presentation--Over 50. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 32)
    - Hills Brother (Box 33)
      - 1. Hills Brother--Raining Beans New/ Rev. I. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 33)
      - 2. Hills Brother--3 spots (hand written note attached). 1982. TRT: 1:30 (Box 33)
      - 3. Hills Brother--Hedonist / Zaremba. 1983. TRT: :30 (Box 33)
    - Hudson River Museum
      - The Exploration of Mars 1978. TRT: :30 (Box 33)
    - Hush Puppies
      - 1. Hush Puppies-- Master #1. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 33)
      - 2. Hush Puppies-- Master #2. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 33)
    - IBM
      - 1. IBM--5 spots. 1988. TRT: 2:30 (Box 33)
      - 2. IBM--CEO Rev. 3 with reaction. 1988. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 33)
      - 3. IBM--3 spots (all MIS/ Partnership Rev. 4). 1988. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 33)
      - 4. IBM--3 spots. Circa 1989. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 33)
      - 5. IBM Corporate--2 spots (both Speech Viewer). 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 33)
      - 6. Corporation--5 spots. 1989. TRT: 2:30 (Box 33)
      - 7. Market Prep--6 spots. 1989. TRT: 3:00 (Box 33)
      - 8. Market Prep--9 spots. 1989. TRT: 4:30 (Box 33)
      - 9. Market Prep--Connectivity. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 33)
      - 10. IBM--3 spots. Circa 1989. TRT: 2:00 (Box 33)
    - IBM (continued) (Box 34)
      - 11. Market Prep--Connectivity Rev. Circa 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 34)
      - 12. Market Prep--9 spots. 1989. TRT: 4:30 (Box 34)
      - 13. IBM--6 spots. 1989. TRT: 4:00 (Box 34)
      - 14. Press Conference Master / Market Driven Campaign--7 spots (4/13/89). 1989. TRT: Circa 3:30 plus (Box 34)
      - 14A. Market Driven Campaign / Press Conference Tuesday Vers. 7 spots (4/11/89). 1989. TRT: Circa 3:30 plus (Box 34)
      - 15. IBM--Teacher / Rev. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 34)
      - 16. IBM--2 spots multi see enclosed list. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
      - 17. Corporate--Space / DMCC. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
      - 18. IBM--3D Silent Forward Logo:. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 34)
      - 19. Education--2 spots (Courseware, News). 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
      - 20. Corporate--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 2:00 (Box 34)
      - 21. Corporate--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
      - 22. Education--2 spots (Rev). 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
      - 23. Corp. Vienna 90. 1989. TRT: :15 (Box 34)
      - 24. Market Prep--Your Business. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
      - 25. Corp.--Target / Jayold (NFA). 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 34)
    - IBM (continued) (Box 35)
      - 26. IBM Corp.--3 spots. 1989. TRT: 2:30 (Box 35)
      - 27. IBM--7 spots. 1990. TRT: 5:30 (Box 35)
      - 28. Corporate 7 spots-- Master (Latest Mix--Old Slates). 1990. TRT: 5:30 (Box 35)
      - 28A. IBM--4 spots Multi Cassette (see enclosed list) -- Master. 1990. TRT: 4:00 (Box 35)
      - 28B. IBM--4 Commercials (with titles). Circa 1990. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 35)
      - 29. Corporate--Vienna 91. 1990. TRT: :15 (Box 35)
      - 30. AS/400--Values / Baldridge Rev. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 31. IBM--Education Alt. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 31A. IBM--Education Alt. 1991. TRT: Circa 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 32. IBM--Education Rev I. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 33. IBM--Multimedia. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 34. IBM--Multimedia Alt. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 35. IBM--Multimedia Rev. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 36. Market Prep / Corporate--2 spots. 1991. TRT: 0.041666667 (Box 35)
      - 37. IBM--Handicapped Center Rev. 1991. TRT: 1:00 (Box 35)
      - 38. IBM--2 spots. 1991. TRT: 2:00 (Box 35)
    - IBM (continued) (Box 36)
      - 39. IBM--6 spots. 1991. TRT: 4:30 (Box 36)
      - 39A. IBM--2 spots (both Manufacturing Rev. 1). 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 36)
      - 39B. IBM--2 spots (both Your Business, Rev. 1). 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 36)
      - 39C. IBM--2 spots (both Environment Rev. 1). 1992. TRT: 1:30 (Box 36)
      - 40. IBM--2 spots (both Handicap Center Rev.). 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 36)
      - 40A. Corporate--2 spots (both Handicap Center Rev.). 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 36)
      - 41. Corporate- 2 spots (both Speech viewer Rev. 1). 1991. TRT: 1:30 (Box 36)
      - 42. Corporate- 2 spots (both Billboard (IBM Logo for PBS Special). 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 36)
      - 43. Corporate--Billboard (IBM Logo for PBS Special). 1991. TRT: :15 (Box 36)
      - 44. Corporate--Americas Libraries Billboard. 1991. TRT: :15 (Box 36)
      - 45. IBM--Creative Spirit Logo. 1992. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 36)
      - 46. From Vienna The New Years Celebration 1992-- Master IBM Billboard IMBB 1025--audio portion, PBS (WNET) produced video portion. 1992. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 36)
      - 47. IBM Corp.--4 spots. 1992. TRT: 2:00 (Box 36)
      - 48. IBM--Logo alt. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 36)
      - 48A. IBM--Logo--Ed McCabe Agency Version. 1992. TRT: Circa :30 (Box 36)
      - 49. IBM--Millennium. 1992. TRT: :15 (Box 36)
    - IBM (continued) (Box 37)
      - 50. Time/ IBM--Inside Time: IBM. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 37)
      - 51. IBM--Skill Dynamics Ad Presentation. 1992. TRT: 4:00 (Box 37)
      - 52. Corporate--Global. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 37)
      - 53. IBM--5 spots (Not for air--for test only). 1993. TRT: 2:30 (Box 37)
      - 54. IBM--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 37)
      - 55. IBM--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 37)
      - 56. Corporate--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 37)
      - 57. Customer Reference--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 37)
      - 58. IBM Image--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 37)
      - 58A. IBM--Customer Service. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 37)
      - 59. IBM--Results. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 37)
      - 60. IBM Image--Global Rev. I (Red Logo). 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 37)
      - 61. IBM--4 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 37)
      - 62. Corporate--Whitbread Sailing. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 37)
      - 63. Corporate--Sailing. 1993. TRT: :30 (Box 37)
      - 64. Olympics--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 37)
    - IBM (continued) (Box 38)
      - 65. Olympics--2 spots. 1993. TRT: 2:00 (Box 38)
      - 66. Olympics--Winning. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 38)
      - 67. IBM Corporate--Environment. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 38)
      - 68. Olympics--4 spot. 1993. TRT: 4:00 (Box 38)
      - 69. Corporate--Rip-O-Matics--2 spots w/ Jay Thomas. 1993. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 38)
      - 70. Corporate--Rip-O-Matics--2 spots w/ Billy Crystal. 1993. TRT: Circa 2:00 (Box 38)
      - 71. Corporate--Rip-O-Matics--3 spots (1 in German). 1993. TRT: Circa 3:00 (Box 38)
      - 73. Open Campaign--Rip-O-Matics--2 spots. 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 38)
      - 74. Always Thinking Rip O Matics--4 spots. 1994. TRT: 4:00 (Box 38)
      - 75. Think What We Can Do Together--Rip-O-Matics--2 spots. 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 38)
      - 76. IBM--2 spots (both Starting Rev. 2). 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 38)
      - 77. IBM--2 spots (both ULF). 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 38)
      - 78. IBM--ULF Rev. 1. 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 38)
      - 79. IBM--ULF Rev. 1. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 38)
      - 80. IBM Corporate--Bobsled Rev. 1. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 38)
      - 81. IBM Corporate--2 spots rev. Master. 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 38)
    - IBM (continued) (Box 39)
      - 82. IBM Corporate--2 spots (both Starting Rev. 3) Master. 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 39)
      - 83. IBM Corporate--2 spots (both ULF Rev. 2). 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 39)
      - 84. IBM--Norwegians Rev. 1. 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 39)
      - 85. IBM--Norwegians Rev. 1 (date indicates duplicate of 84). 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 39)
      - 86. Olympics--2 spots (both Bobsled). 1994. TRT: 1:30 (Box 39)
      - 87. Olympics--Bobsled Rev. 2. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 39)
      - 88. Corporate--2 spots (both /PTVO). 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 39)
      - 89. IBM--8 spots-- Master. 1994. TRT: Circa 5:00 (Box 39)
      - 90. Corporate--2 spots (Rip-o Matics). 1994. TRT: 2:00 (Box 39)
      - 91. IBM--Generic Sports. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 39)
      - 92. IBM--Generic Sports Rev. 1994. TRT: :30 (Box 39)
      - 93. Sherrie--2 spots (IBM Open, Open Intl.). 1994. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 39)
      - R-1. IBM Master R-1 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 39)
      - R-2. IBM Master R-2 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 39)
      - R-3. IBM Master R-3 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 39)
      - R-4. IBM Master R-4 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 39)
    - ITT (Technology Institute/ Corp.) (Box 40)
      - 1. ITT--3 spots (all Corporate Umbrella TV) Master. Circa 1987. TRT: 2:00 (Box 40)
      - 2. ITT--3 spots (all Corporate Umbrella TV) Master (different date from #1) (case damaged). 1987. TRT: 2:00 (Box 40)
      - 3. Corporate--Gallon Fluid Technology. 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 40)
      - 4. ITT--2 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 40)
      - 5. Corporate--2 spots. 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 40)
      - 6. Corporate III Revised. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 40)
      - 7. ITT--Technology Institute / Corp. 1988. TRT: :30 (Box 40)
      - 8. ITT--Corp Lift (22 versions--see enclosed list). 1988. TRT: 11:00 (Box 40)
      - 9. Corporate--2 spots. 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 40)
      - 9A. Corporate--2 spots (duplicate of #9--reverse order). 1989. TRT: 1:00 (Box 40)
      - 10. Corporate--6 spots. 1989. TRT: 3:00 (Box 40)
      - 10A. Corporate--5 spots (duplicates of 5 spots on #10). 1989. TRT: 2:30 (Box 40)
      - 11. Corporate--Automotive Rev. 89. 1989. TRT: :30 (Box 40)
      - 12. Corporate--3 spots. 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 40)
      - 13. ITT Corp.--Very Special Arts. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 40)
      - 14. Corporate--3 spots. Circa 1990. TRT: 1:30 (Box 40)
    - ITT (Technology Institute/ Corp.) (continued) (Box 41)
      - 15. Sheraton Sales Video--The Natural Choice. 1990. TRT: 6:38 (Box 41)
      - 16. ITT (No Slates) --4 spots. Circa 1991. TRT: 2:00 (Box 41)
      - 17. Corporate--4 spots. 1991. TRT: 2:00 (Box 41)
      - 18. Educational Service--They Say / Jobs. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 41)
      - 18A. Educational Service--They Say / Jobs (different date). 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 41)
      - 19. Corporate--4 spots. 1992. TRT: 2:00 (Box 41)
      - 19A. Corporate--4 spots (different order than #19). 1992. TRT: 2:00 (Box 41)
      - 20. ITT Automotive--ITT Automotive Detroit Grand Prix. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 41)
      - 21. ITT Automotive--ITT Automotive Detroit Grand Prix (date different than #20). 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 41)
      - 22. ITT Hartford Tough Nurse Rev. 1. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 41)
      - 23. ITT Hartford--Not a Doctor. 1992. TRT: :30 (Box 41)
      - 24. Corp--5 spots. 1993. TRT: 3:00 (Box 41)
      - 25. Corporate--2 spots (Sheraton, Technical Institute). 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 41)
      - 26. Corporate--ITT Sheraton 93 Rev. 2cc. 1993. TRT: 1:00 (Box 41)
      - 27. ITT Corporate--2 spots (both World Cup Soccer--1 in Spanish). 1994. TRT: 1:00 (Box 41)
      - 28. ITT Corporate--Three Tenors Billboard. 1994. TRT: :15 (Box 41)
    - ITT (Technology Institute/ Corp.) (continued) (Box 42)
      - 29. ITT Corporate--6 spots. Circa 1994. TRT: 3:00 (Box 42)
      - 30. ITT Nightvision--After Dark Rev. End Tag. 1995. TRT: :30 (Box 42)
      - 31. ITT Corporate--David Frost Billboard. 1995. TRT: :15 (Box 42)
      - 32. ITT Corp--3 spots. 1995. TRT: 1:30 (Box 42)
      - 33 BB Rev. ITT Corp--David Frost Billboard Rev. 1995. TRT: :15 (Box 42)
      - ITT--Ceasar's Temp Dub Source. Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 42)
      - Corporate--ITT Historical Reel. 1990. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 42)
    - Jack In the Box
      - #1. 12 spots tied (list on cover). 1983. TRT: 6:00 (Box 42)
      - 2. 13 spots (see enclosed log). 1982. TRT: 6:30 (Box 42)
      - 3. 3 spots. 1985. TRT: 1:30 (Box 42)
      - 4. 3 spots tied-- Master. 1985. TRT: 1:30 (Box 42)
      - 8/9/1984. 8 spot. 1984. TRT: 4:00 (Box 42)
      - Master #1. Master Reel #1 (attached sticky reads Taco Music 30). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 42)
      - Master R-2. Master Reel #2 (list enclosed) Circa 60 spots. 1979-1981. TRT: Over 30:00 (Box 42)
    - Junior Achievement
      - 1. Junior Achievement--4 spots (all Making It). 1982. TRT: 2:00 (Box 42)
      - 2. Project Business--PSA--Dinah Shore. 1982. TRT: 3:00 (Box 42)
      - 3. AR. Achievement Workshop. 1980. TRT: 1:00 (Box 42)
    - JC Penney (Box 43)
      - Master Reel #1 (no list). Undated. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 43)
    - King Cola
      - 1. King Cola Sales Film:. 1979. TRT: 9:00 (Box 43)
      - 2. 2 spots (both Announcement). 1979. TRT: 1:30 (Box 43)
      - 3. 4 spots. 1979. TRT: 1:40 (Box 43)
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance
      - 1. 4 spots. 1985. TRT: 2:30 (Box 43)
      - 2. America Believes in Liberty Master. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)
      - 3. Something to Believe In Rev. #3. 1985. TRT: 20:00 (Box 43)
      - 4. Swing Easy. 1985. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)
      - 5. 2 spots (both America Believes in Liberty Rev.) Master. 1985. TRT: 1:30 (Box 43)
      - 6. 4 spots. 1985. TRT: 2:30 (Box 43)
      - 7. Workers Compensation. 1985. TRT: :30 (Box 43)
      - 8. Tips From Legends. 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)
      - 9. Corporate Rev. 4. 1986. TRT: 1:00 (Box 43)
      - 10. America Believes in Liberty/ Homeowners Rev. 1 Master. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 43)
      - 11. Happy Birthday. 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 43)
      - 12. 2 spots (both Liberty for All). 1986. TRT: :30 (Box 43)
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance (continued) (Box 44)
      - 13. Liberty for All-- Rev. II. Circa 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 44)
      - 14. 7 spots (all More). 1987. TRT: 2:45 (Box 44)
      - 14A. 7 spots-- (duplicate of #14 w/ slates). 1987. TRT: 2:45 (Box 44)
      - 15. 2 spots-- (both../Legend of the Game--:30, :60). 1987. TRT: 3:00 (Box 44)
      - 16. 2 spots (both More Rev.). 1987. TRT: :30 (Box 44)
      - 17. 7 spots (all More). 1987. TRT: 2:15 (Box 44)
      - 18. 9 spots (list enclosed). 1987. TRT: 1:00 (Box 44)
      - 19. 18 Tips Video (golf). 1988. TRT: 1:00 (Box 44)
      - 20. 1988--Advertising Legends. 1988. TRT: 13:54 (Box 44)
      - 21. 4 spots. 1989. TRT: 2:00 (Box 44)
      - 22. 1989 Sales Convention Film. 1989. TRT: 12:49 (Box 44)
      - 23. 7 spots. 1989. TRT: 2:45 (Box 44)
      - 24. Sales Presentation Film with Revised :30 commercials (no list). 1989. TRT: Not indicated. (Box 44)
      - 25. 2 spots (both Dominoes Alt. Master). 1990. TRT: 1:00 (Box 44)
      - 26. 10 spots. 1990. TRT: 5:00 (Box 44)
      - 27. Revised Mix--James Dean. 1990. TRT: :30 (Box 44)
    - Liberty Mutual Insurance (continued) (Box 45)
      - 28. James Dean Revised. 1991. TRT: :30 (Box 45)